(Man:)As a matter of fact I do.
(Man:)At a little place
called the DMV.
(Raj:)He's got him there.
(Raj:)The D even stands
for department.
Excuse me!
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
can I please
(Sheldon:)see a show of hands?
(Sheldon:)Who here takes issue with
this person cutting the line?
(Man:)Told you.
(Sheldon:)Well, what a sad
state of affairs!
(Sheldon:)That you've all been
so ground down
(Sheldon:)by life, you don't even notice
when someone disrespects you.
(Howard:)I can't believe
we're gonna get beat up,
(Howard:)and it's not
because of your chair.
(Sheldon:)You know, right now,
at the back of this line,
(Sheldon:)there's a movie fan
like you
(Sheldon:)who's not going to get in,
(Sheldon:)because this person
simply doesn't care.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, 61 years ago,
(Sheldon:)there was another person
at the back of the line
(Sheldon:)and her name
was Rosa Parks.
(Leonard:)Okay, you may have
to pretend you're black
(Leonard:)to get us out of here.
(Sheldon:)Now, let's follow in that
brave woman's footsteps,
and stand up for ourselves!